ROGER C. HOUSE

2810 Richland Park Dr. **Bryant, AR 72022** Cell: (501) 314-0228

Email: rchouse@live.com

Objective:

My goal is to obtain gainful employment as an IT Professional. I will provide my depth of knowledge and experience that I have gained over many years working with Information Technology and computer related services. I will strive to complete the duties established by my employer and/or their associates and become proficient in my duties. I shall work diligently with others within my specified group(s) to accomplish all assigned tasks on time.

Education: Remington College

19 Remington Dr.

Little Rock, AR 72204

Graduate of 2008 G.P.A 3.9

Associate of Computer Science Computer Networking Administration

Academic Awards: Perfect Attendance

Dean's List (3 consecutive years)

Presidents Honors

Graduate: Summa cum laude

School Activities: National Technical Honor Society

Student Ambassador Program: Night Planner

Computer Club: Treasurer

Skills and Abilities:

- Computer Hardware Upgrade Suggestions and Installation
- **Computer Software and Programming**
- **Computer Networking Administration**
- **Network Implementation Strategies**
- Computer Repair and Maintenance
- Microsoft Sever Side Software Administration
- Virus Detection and Elimination
- **IT Security Protocols**
- Intrusion Detection and Protection
- **Network Traffic Analyzation**
- **Help Desk Procedures**
- Strict adherence to HIPAA guidelines.

Qualifying Traits: I am a skilled, highly self-motivated, extremely goal oriented, team player with a desire for exceeding my own expectations. I have a tremendous amount of knowledge in both related and unrelated fields of study that undoubtedly gives me further insight into problem-solving and troubleshooting.

I am very punctual and organized. I am also currently seeking out new areas of concentration and soon plan on completing several IT certifications. I would be a valuable asset for any company to acquire. I work extremely well with others and I always do my best to bring positivity and motivation to all those I meet. I conduct myself with professionalism and courtesy.

Personal responsibility and accountability is a trait you can always depend on me to possess. I've worked with computers since I was a child and IT has continued to be a passion of mine until the present. I want to improve upon my skills and further my education to ensure I continue to provide my employer with the very best resources at my disposal, including my dedication and talents that will help make their business an even greater success.

Work History:

Don Stephens Trucking & Const. Inc.

9526 Brittany Point Dr. Starting Position: Assistant Manager Ending Position: Assistant Manager Little Rock, AR 72206

Start/End: 11/2008 - 10/2016

501-416-6227 (Terrell Stephens)

Positions Held:

Assistant Manager (Warehouse Operations)

Duties:

The daily operation and closing of the Little Rock Air Force Base FMS Warehouse; where it was my extreme pleasure to serve the brave, proud and strong men and women of the United States Armed Forces. As a government contractor my responsibilities included:

- Receiving and fulfilling orders for delivery of furnishings.
- Hiring and managing work crews of up to 6 people.
- Training staff and employees on a quarterly basis.
- Providing furnishings and appliances to 11, 76 room dorms.
- Working in conjunction with Air Force staff, military leaders, civilians and contractors to complete mission critical tasks on time.
- Inventorying, storing and securing federally funded assets.
- Planning and implementing efficient warehouse storage schemes.
- Performing maintenance tasks on the FMS' trucking fleet.
- Tracking and maintaining all federally funded assets.
- Securing all FMS warehouse assets from loss or damage.
- Following strict OSHA, fire and safety regulations.
- Maintaining strict adherence to HIPAA guidelines.

ENTITY: Doyne Incorporated

719 Main St.

North Little Rock, AR 72119-9210

Phone: 501-374-6532 (Dexter Doyne)

Start/End: 11/2007 – 11/2008

Starting Position: Shop Tech

Ending Position: Master Builder

Starting Position: Warehouse Assistant Ending Position: Office Assistant

Positions Held: Warehouse Assistant

Office Assistant

Duties: It was my proud responsibly to receive furniture and appliance shipments for the men

and women of the United States Air Force. In addition I was also responsible for the inventorying, tracking, delivery and final placement of said items. Later I was placed in

an office environment which expanded my duties to include customer service, organizing shipment and deliveries and maintaining a safe office/warehouse

environment.

ENTITY: Wood Concepts Inc. Start/End: 03/2002 – 08/2005

3426 Mundo Rd North Little Rock, AR

501-888-5324 (Roger Morris)

Positions Held: Shop tech

Drawer and face-frame assembler Shipping and receiving foreman Sanding and finishing tech Custom cabinet installation tech

Box builder assistant Master Builder

Duties: It was my responsibility to prepare, manufacture, assemble, deliver and install

custom cabinets for Wood Concepts exceptional clients. These procedures involved the ordering of supplies, use of dangerous and specialized equipment

and high degree of skill and focus to create a beautiful finished product.

References

Alfred JR Owens 501 Wellington Ct. Jacksonville, AR 72076 Lowe's Store Manager 501-681-4611

Jason Newburn 501 Lamar Dr. Burbank, CA 92107 Heart Hospital RN 501-213-7211 Dyann Flowers 10712 Cactus Cove Alexander, AR 72027 AHDC Manager 501-317-0688

Juan Newburn 5 London Circle Little Rock, AR 72209 Adleta Manager 501-681-1361